<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CountryProfile</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_name">BANGLADESH</string>
    <string name="india_name">INDIA</string>
    <string name="pakistan_name">PAKISTAN</string>

    <string name="bdtext"> Bangladesh, to the east of India on the Bay of Bengal,
        is a South Asian country marked by lush greenery and many waterways.
        Its Padma (Ganges), Meghna and Jamuna rivers create fertile plains, and travel by boat is common.
        On the southern coast, the Sundarbans, an enormous mangrove forest shared with Eastern India,
        is home to the royal Bengal tiger.\n\n
        
        Capital: Dhaka\n
        Dialing code: +880\n
        President: Abdul Hamid\n
        Population: 163 million (2019)\n
        Gross domestic product: 302.6 billion USD (2019)\n
    </string>
    <string name="indiatext"> India, officially the Republic of India, is a country in South Asia.
        It is the second-most populous country, the seventh-largest country by land area,
        and the most populous democracy in the world.\n\n
        
        President: Ram Nath Kovind Trending\n
        Capital: New Delhi\n
        Dialing code: +91\n
        Area: 3.287 million km²\n
        Population: 1.366 billion (2019) \n
        Prime minister: Narendra Modi\n
    
    </string>

    <string name="pakistantext">

        Pakistan, officially the Islamic Republic of Pakistan, is a country in South Asia.
        It is the world\'s fifth-most populous country, with a population exceeding 225.2 million, and has the world\'s second-largest Muslim population.
        Pakistan is the 33rd-largest country by area, spanning 881,913 square kilometres.\n\n

        Prime minister: Imran Khan Trending\n
        Capital: Islamabad\n
        Dialing code: +92\n
        President: Arif Alvi\n
        Population: 216.6 million (2019) World Bank\n
    </string>

    <string name="mayanmarText">
        
        Myanmar (formerly Burma) is a Southeast Asian nation of more than 100 ethnic groups,
        bordering India, Bangladesh, China, Laos and Thailand. Yangon (formerly Rangoon),
        the country\'s largest city, is home to bustling markets, numerous parks and lakes, and the towering,
        gilded Shwedagon Pagoda, which contains Buddhist relics and dates to the 6th century.
        \n\n
        Capital: Naypyitaw\n
        Area: 676,575 km²\n
        Population: 54.05 million (2019)\n
        Currency: Myanmar kyat\n
        Gross domestic product: 76.09 billion USD (2019) \n



    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_bangladeshsubactivity">Bangladeshsubactivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

</resources>